你知道我最喜歡人類什麼嗎？  屍骨很好堆疊
You know what I like about people?  They stack so well.
我幫你收一下
Let me get this for you.
- 還要看嗎？  - 不了
-Want the paper?  -No.
- 太多了  - 根本不夠
-This is too much.  -It's not half enough.
多謝你特別為我營業
Thanks for opening up for me.
隨時隨地，你知道的
Anytime day or night. You know that.
整個城市的人都拼了命要創新
In a town where everyone  is so carefully reinventing themselves,
我就喜歡弗萊迪連裝都懶得裝
what I like about Freddy is  that he doesn't even pretend to change.
我遲到了
I'm late.
每週二我都和發言人  和多數黨領袖會面
Every Tuesday I sit down with  the Speaker and the Majority Leader
討論當周的議程  討論這個詞或許不恰當
to discuss the week's agenda.  Well, discuss is probably the wrong word.
是他倆滔滔不絕，我靜坐在旁  想像這兩人下油鍋的模樣
They talk while I sit quietly and imagine  their lightly-salted faces frying in a skillet.
瓦克斯一定在挫著等吧
Vasquez must be shitting herself.
她和沃克兩人都是
Shitting herselfwhile Walker is  shitting himself
然後她再幫他擦屁股
then shoveling his shit on her shit.
鮑伯，我還想吃飯
Bob, I'm planning on eating.
決定好後補提案了嗎？
Do we have a back-up on the docket?
- 你搞得定吧，法蘭？  - 我和我的人在…
-You're on that, right, Frank?  -I'm working with my staff...
共和黨的那些傢伙  一定會拿這事堵我們
The Republicans are gonna  ram this up our ass.
要是我就會
I would if I was them.
就算眾議院勉強通過  參議院也會毀了提案
Well, even if we squeak it through the House,  watch them mangle it in the Senate.
- 或是阻礙  - 若是這提案一定如此
-Or filibuster it.  -Well, sure, if it looks anything like this.
我不知道沃克為何硬要螳臂擋車
I don't know why Walker's  trying to tackle a charging elephant.
簡直是瘋了
It's madness.
議員，很抱歉打擾你  但我看到你坐在這…
Congressman, sorry to interrupt,  but I saw you sitting over here and...
瑞米，各位，這位是瑞米丹頓
Remy. Gentlemen, this is Remy Danton.
瑞米，這位是發言人柏許  和議員…
Remy, this is Speaker Birch,  and Congressman...
我早久仰大名  發言人先生、議員
I'm well aware.  Mister Speaker, Congressman.
瑞米升上葛蘭頓希爾的合夥人
Remy just made partner at Glendon Hill.
葛蘭頓希爾？  很優秀的團隊，恭喜你
Glendon Hill?  Great team over there. Congratulations.
謝謝
Thank you.
他們上次找合夥人是何時？
When was the last time they added a partner?
- 有一陣子了  - 他們是不會放過人才的
-It's been a while.  -Well, they know a winner when they see one.
瑞米是我所見過最好的新聞秘書
Remy was the best press  secretary I ever had.
- 那你怎麼放他走？  - 我沒有，是他們來挖角
-Why'd you let him go?  -I didn't. They stole him away.
你的客戶有哪些人？
What accounts do you have?
善可工業是主要客戶之一
SanCorp lndustries is my main one.
現在由我接管
I run that account now.
不打擾你了，真抱歉
Anyhow, I'll let you get back to it.  Sorry again to interrupt.
- 沒問題  - 幸會
-No problem.  -Very nice to meet you both.
老天，這些政治掮客越來越年輕了
Christ, these lobbyists keep  getting younger and younger.
他賺的搞不好比我們加起來還要多
He's probably making more than  all of us combined.
這餐我請吧，我去買單
Gentlemen, this one's on me.  I'm gonna track down that check.
葛蘭頓希爾代表善可工業
Glendon Hill fronts SanCorp lndustries.
善可工業涉入自然氣  我對自然氣一點興趣也沒有
SanCorp is deep into natural gas.  I don't give a hoot about natural gas.
但我下頭還有67個副黨鞭  他們可都需要競選資金
But I have 67 deputy whips  and they all need cash to win races.
善可工業幫我收買人心  條件是收買我的心
SanCorp helps me purchase loyalty  and in return, they expect mine.
很不要臉，我知道  但口袋這麼深時，人人都想排隊
It's degrading, I know. But when the tit's  that big, everybody gets in line.
跟他們說我搞定
Tell them I'm on top of it.
光一句話可不夠
I need more than that.
你很清楚這種事  我是不會搞砸的，瑞米
You are well aware that I do not drop the  ball on things like this, Remy.
承諾，法蘭
Promises, Frank.
國務卿、阿根廷  海外石油開採客戶…
The Secretary of State, Argentina,  the offshore drilling accounts...
等我解決問題後再說
Talk to me when I've solved the problem.
我在解決問題時別浪費我時間
Don't waste my time  when I'm working on solving it.
這可是上億的資金  你不能不回我電話
When there's billions on the line,  you can't not call me back
- 我也不能不來  - 好啦，幸苦你了
-and I can't not show up.  -Fine. Thank you for your diligence.
給你和民主黨  國會競選委員會八位數
Eight figures to you and the D triple C.
六百萬給你建以你命名的圖書館
Six million to build that library ofyours,  in your name.
我知道
I know.
別逼他們下次選舉時  送錢給你的對手
Don't make them throw money  at your challenger next cycle.
- 你說得很清楚了  - 是嗎？
-You've made your point.  -Have l?
最好是這樣
I hope so.
真浪費人才
Such a waste of talent.
他選擇金錢過於權勢
He chose money over power.
這城市幾乎所有人都會犯的錯
In this town, a mistake  nearly everyone makes.
金錢只是買了十年  就開始毀壞的別墅
Money is the McMansion in Sarasota  that starts falling apart after 10 years.
權勢卻是幾世紀  都屹立不搖的石造建築
Power is the old stone building  that stands for centuries.
我無法尊敬那些  看不清這點的人
I cannot respect someone  who doesn't see the difference.
這是什麼？
What am I looking at?
- 《威廉學報》  - 威廉…
-The Williams Register.  -Williams...
- 大學，1978年9月  - 為什麼要看這個？
-College. September '78.  -And why am I looking at it?
社論
The editorial.
沒什麼啊
Not that interesting.
麥克凱恩母校威廉大學  看看刊頭
Michael Kern went to Williams.  Check out the masthead.
還有這個
And then there's this.
這太牽拖了吧
It's thin.
他太完美了，完美無瑕
The guy's a unicorn. He pisses rainbows.
- 你認為這能引起關注嗎？  - 我認為你可以
-You think we can get traction with this?  -I think you could.
琳達瓦克斯在電話上
Linda Vasquez is on the phone.
沒想到這麼久才打來
I'm surprised it took her this long.
才9點6分
It's only six past 9:00.
表示她三小時前讀完《先軀報》
Which means she read the Herald  three hours ago
然後給總統罵了兩個半小時
and spent the past two and a half  getting reamed by the President.
跟她說我這就過去
Tell her I'm on my way.
你應該要管好唐納的  你向我保證…
You were supposed to keep Donald in line.  You assured me...
他推行這議程已經25年了
Twenty-five years he's been pushing  this particular agenda.
我們只是掃到颱風尾  小挫折罷了
We got between the mother bear and her cub.  It's a setback, that's all.
這是就職第一天
On our first day in office.
琳達，我在四位總統下任職過
Linda, I've worked with four presidents.
這麼大的提案  一定會碰到很多挫折的
Setbacks are a dime a dozen  with a bill of this size.
法蘭，你若管不住…
Frank, if you can't control this...
我很不喜歡  被人指使該怎麼做事，琳達
I don't take well to being  micromanaged, Linda.
不然你來做我的工作好嗎？
You want to do my job for me  and run the White House?
祝你好運，我不會擋你路
Good luck. I won't stand in your way.
好，法蘭，由你全權負責
Okay, Frank. Fine. This is yours now.
若這提案在百日內  不能在國會通過決議
If this thing can't make it to the floor  in the first hundred days,
我就讓你去跟總統解釋  他為什麼欺騙美國人民
then I'll let you explain to the President  why he lied to the American people.
我要回去上班了
I'm gonna get back to work.
請自便
Please do.
我們應該改約週五  而不是週三
We really should be doing this  on a Friday instead of a Wednesday.
因為週五的話  大家還有週末可以消化
Because if we do it on a Friday,  people have the weekend.
好吧，那就週五
Fine, we'll do it on Friday.
文件都準備好了嗎？
Is all the paperwork ready?
資深員工比較麻煩  有資遣費以及…
Some of the more senior people are trickier.  There's severance and...
- 但不該有法律問題  - 沒有
-But we shouldn't run into any legal issues.  -No, no.
我們和員工簽訂的  都是自由僱傭合約
We use at-will employment contracts  across the board.
週五一早就開始
We'll get started first thing Friday.
午餐前要完成  所有員工的離職面談
I want all of the  exit interviews done by lunch.
克萊兒，我真的覺得這樣不妥
Claire, I just can't help but think  that this is a mistake.
- 我們已經談過，艾薇琳  - 我知道
-We've discussed this already, Evelyn.  -I know, I know.
我這麼說只是為了我的良知
But I just have to say it  for the sake of my conscience.
我覺得你這樣做
I think that you are dismantling
拆散了我們十年來的努力，我…
what we have built over  the past 10 years and l...
我覺得你處理這事的方法…
And I think the way you're handling this is...
- 很殘忍  - 這不是件易事，艾薇琳
-ls cruel.  -It's not easy, Evelyn.
但是必要的
But it's necessary.
你總是要我對你誠實以待
You have always asked me  to be honest with you.
這是我們的工作模式
That's how we work together.
我若不認同就直說
I disagree with something, I say it.
我全然不認同
Well, I disagree 100 percent.
拜託你，克萊兒，別這麼做
Please, Claire, don't do this.
我尊重你的想法，艾薇琳
I respect your opinion, Evelyn.
我也感謝你告訴我  但我是不會改變心意的
And I appreciate you sharing it with me.  But I'm not going to change my mind.
那就週五吧
Friday, then.
若這是你的意思
If that's what you want.
這是大改革，全然的革新
This is major reform. A complete overhaul.
通常要好幾個月時間
That would usually take months.
我們只有幾天，沒有幾個月
Well, we only have days, not months.
但過程不能直接…
But think about the process. We can't just...
當我詢問我的同事  你們的老闆們
When I asked my colleagues, your bosses,
也是教育界的佼佼者
who are the smartest minds in education,
你們是從百人當中挑選出來的
out of hundreds, we arrived at you.
在場的這六個人
The six of you in this room.
我知道這是個苦差事
Now I realize it is a difficult task.
但我們有改變歷史的機會
But we have the opportunity  to make history here.
我希望我們一起完成
And I want all of us to make it together.
祝你們好運，萬事拜託了
So, good luck. We're counting on you.
第一頁
Page one.
這些要點反映提案的中心思想
These bullet points reflect the  key planks at the center of our bill.
快適應吧  我們要搞定草案初稿才能離開
Get comfy. This is your home  until we have a presentable first draft.
唐納，今早真是瘋狂
Donald, what a morning.
我真不知道他們怎麼弄到手的
I have no idea how they got this.
我特別交代下去  要處理得乾乾淨淨
I specifically told my staff  to destroy everything.
- 真想不到…  - 無所謂
-I can't imagine...  -lt doesn't matter how it happened.
現在為時已晚  我們只好見招拆招了
We can't make it un-happen.  So now we have to adapt.
他們不知道這只是草案初稿嗎？
Don't they realize that this is a first draft?
其實說穿了只是角度問題
All we have here really  is a perception problem.
但第一印象只有一次機會  你明白的，唐納
We don't get a second chance at  a first impression, Donald. You know that.
我跟你可是同一陣線
Now, look, I'm on your side.
但琳達氣瘋了
But Linda is furious.
- 她說什麼？  - 他們需要待罪羔羊
-What's she saying?  -They want to point fingers.
- 我嗎？  - 我跟她說不行
-At me?  -I told her we cannot do that.
這個過程不能沒有你
I mean, you are vital to this process.
我真的受夠他們了，唐納
I'm up to here with them, Donald.
欺騙，棄你於不顧
For lying, for turning their back on you.
我甚至想說「去他的」
You know, I'm of a mind to say "screw it."
我來頂算了，氣氣他們
I'll fall on this grenade myself  just to piss them off.
幫我接CNN的約翰金
Get me John King at CNN.
等等，法蘭，這不是你的錯
Wait, Frank. This is not your fault.
不，我們必須保護你的名聲
No, we have to protect your reputation.
但你才是要在眾議院  推行此提案的人
But you're the man that needs to get  the bill through the House.
我會的，等等  我會交給下面的副手
I will. Hang on.  I will assign it to one of my deputies
私下搞定  我會告訴你該怎麼做
and quietly manage it.  And I'll help guide you through the process.
- 我覺得不是很妥當  - 不然你說該怎麼辦？
-I am not comfortable with this.  -Well, then, what do you suggest we do?
烈士最希望的就是能壯烈犧牲
What a martyr craves more than  anything is a sword to fall on.
劍就由你來拿
So, you sharpen the blade,  hold it at just the right angle,
然後，3、2、1…
and then, three, two, one...
應該是我
It should be me.
- 這是我的提案  - 不行
-lt was my bill.  -No, impossible.
唐納，教育是你畢生的心血
Donald, education has been your life's work.
老實說，我早沒了鬥志
The truth is my heart is not in this fight.
你也知道我不擅長談判  我可以寫政策
You know me. I'm not a wheeler-dealer.  I can put my mind to policy,
但政治的勾心鬥角  不是我的強項
but I'm no good at this brand of politics.
捨你其誰呢？
Well, if not you, then who?
應該是你，法蘭
It should be you, Frank.
你很傑出，大家都敬重你
You're formidable. People respect you.
他們會跟隨你  這次讓我靠邊站就好
They will follow your lead.  Let me be on the sidelines for this.
要我答應這件事  我必須先知道
Well, I could only consider that  as an option if I knew
我還能尋求你的幫助
that I could still come to you for counsel.
當然
Of course.
只要你有需要
Whatever you need.
某部分的我暗自竊喜  這次新聞走漏的事
Part of me is glad this got leaked.
沒走漏當然比較理想
Well, it would've been better if it hadn't
但至少大家都清楚我的立場
but at least people know where I stand.
謝謝你，唐納
Thank you, Donald.
我很樂意，法蘭
Happy to do it, Frank.
他根本不知道隔壁有六個小子
He has no idea we got  six kids in the next room
已經在寫新草案了，史坦普！
already working on a new draft. Stamper!
幹嘛壞了他的好心情？  我們剛送了他一份大禮
But why dampen his mood by telling him?  We just gave him a great gift.
完成他的使命
The chance to fulfill his destiny.
幫布萊斯寫份新聞稿
Write up a statement for Blythe.
讓位、新點子，諸如此類的
Stepping aside, fresh ideas,  et cetera, et cetera.
要慎重一點，他是個好人
Make it dignified. He's a good man.
把《威廉學報》的社論給我
And bring me that Williams editorial.
我有東西給你，今晚見  已傳送給喬伊邦斯
在鄭重考慮  以及和身邊的人討論後
After careful thought and  discussion with my staff,
我決定讓出  教育改革法案的管理權
I am relinquishing my management  of the Education Reform Act.
我希望能夠繼續參與這過程  但我將不會直接…
I hope to remain a part of the process,  but I won't be working...
你為何洩出草案？
Why did you leak the draft?
我不是很清楚是如何洩漏的
I'm not exactly sure how it got leaked
- 但這確實代表…  - 但是從你辦公室洩出，是嗎？
-but it does represent...  -lt came from your office though, correct?
- 是我們寫的…  - 那提案將由誰接管？
-We wrote it...  -Who will be managing the bill now?
- 法蘭安德沃  - 是你的人選嗎？
-Frank Underwood.  -Was that your choice?
還是總統府…
Or did the administration...
將提案交託給法蘭  我非常有信心
I feel very confident  placing the bill in Frank's capable hands.
邦斯小姐
Ms. Barnes.
你胃口還真大
How very Deep Throat of you.
我是沒法幫你搞掉總統  參議員如何？
Well, I can't help you dispatch a president.  How about a senator?
關於大衛營協議的社論
The editorial on the Camp David Accords.
「此報認為卡特總統  應該要求以色列
"lt is the opinion of this newspaper  that President Carter demand lsrael
「從加薩走廊和約旦河西岸  撤離所有市民…
"withdraw all its citizens from  the Gaza Strip and West Bank..."
「他們自1967年  就非法侵佔此地區」
"Which it has illegally occupied since 1967."
「非法侵佔」
"lllegally occupied."
很煽動的言論，不是嗎？
That's quite an incendiary quote,  don't you think?
對於一個自稱  中東是外交首要的總統府
For an administration that says the  Middle East is its top foreign policy priority.
麥克凱恩？
Michael Kern?
是他親筆寫的？
Did he personally write the editorial?
他當時是編輯
He was the editor.
但是他自己寫的嗎？
But did he write it himself?
不然就沒新聞性了
Then there's no story.
我只是說這是個值得問的問題
I'm saying it's a question worth asking.
若他否認有關聯呢？
And if he denies involvement?
他一定會，就讓他
He will. Let him.
這人想要獲准出任國務卿
This is a man trying to be confirmed  as Secretary of State.
任何故事都有新聞性
Everything is a story.
沒有直接的連接
There's no direct link.
翰默史密不會批的
I can't get this past Hammerschmidt.
牢牢記住你反抗我的這一刻
Remember this moment  when you resisted me.
當你說出  「不然就沒新聞性了」
When you said the words,  "Then there is no story."
好好睡一覺吧，邦斯小姐
Get a good night's sleep, Ms. Barnes.
明天可有你忙的
You have a big day tomorrow.
法蘭斯？
Francis?
這是什麼？
What is this?
看來像什麼？
What does it look like?
但地下室是我的地盤
But the basement is mine.
我知道
I know.
- 不是給我的  - 那是誰的？
-It's not for me.  -So who's it for?
你啊
For you.
國會大樓有健身房
There's a gym in the Capitol.
你從來不去
Which you never use.
因為我忙著治理國家
Because I'm a tad busy running the country.
但在家時沒有啊  你現在可沒藉口了
But not at home.  So now you have no excuse.
- 搬出去  - 先試試嘛
-I want it out.  -Give it a try first.
你是想暗示我中年發福嗎？
Is this your subtle way  of saying that I'm out of shape?
不，我只是想建議你  身材可以更好
No. It's my way of suggesting  you could be in better shape.
那聽起來很後恭前倨  也很自視甚高
That sounds both passive-aggressive  and condescending.
只是很直接了當
Just plain aggressive and true.
- 別等我了  - 你現在要去跑步？
-Don't wait up for me.  -Are you going running now?
對，我今早因為開會  所以沒時間去
Yes, because I couldn't this morning.  I had an early meeting.
用這玩意吧，外面很冷
Use the monstrosity. It's freezing out.
留給你去適應吧
You break it in.
真的很像中古世紀的刑具
It looks positively medieval, doesn't it?
把我唯一的私人空間  變成健身地牢，我絕不允許
Trying to turn my only sanctuary  into a fitness dungeon. I won't have it.
有點扯
It's a stretch.
我們沒有在誤導別人  他當時是編輯
We're not misleading anyone.  He was the editor.
- 打電話問發言了嗎？  - 試了三次
-Did you call for comment?  -I tried three times.
新聞秘書說會回我電話  結果都沒有
The press secretary said he'd get  back to me, he didn't.
背景調查呢？  沒有支持這社論的東西嗎？
What about research? You couldn't  find anything to echo the editorial?
發言？其他相關新聞？
No quotes? No op-ed pieces?
如果有的話  你不覺得早有人登了嗎？
Don't you think if something like that existed  someone would have printed it by now?
別人沒有這消息，盧卡斯
Nobody else has this, Lucas.
- 我不認為這具有新聞性  - 我沒說這有
-I don't think there's a story here.  -I'm not saying there's a story.
我只是說  這裏有個需要解答的問題
All I'm saying is that there's a question  that needs to be answered.
這可是國務卿人選
This is a nominee for Secretary of State.
我們手上有關於  巴勒斯坦跟以色列的社論
We have an editorial on Palestine and lsrael.
- 不是他寫的  - 這點還不清楚
-Which he didn't write.  -Which we don't know he didn't write.
正是
Exactly.
我們不一定要登
We don't have to print it.
我可以掃瞄後上傳  然後再推文
I could just scan the thing,  stick it on a site and tweet the link.
不過別家報社可能會…
But if I did that, some other paper might...
別耍賤
Don't be a bitch.
我會跟湯姆說
I'll talk to Tom.
我也只有這點要求
That's all I was asking.
我們不能讓…
We simply can't afford to allow...
我有個人選，非常適合
I got a guy, he's almost perfect.
自由意志主義的毒蟲  泡在活動房屋中
He's a libertarian drug fiend  marinating in a mobile home.
有許多事我和雷根總統  都是立場相左
I didn't agree with  President Reagan on many things.
但所謂的滴流經濟學  確實有優點
But there was some merit  to the notion of trickle-down economics.
我認為滴流外交也是如此
And I feel there is much merit  to the idea of trickle-down diplomacy.
這原本是我的詞  一定是瓦克斯給他的
Those are my lines.  Vasquez must have given them to him.
解決巴勒斯坦  和以色列膠著的關係
...solve the stalemate between  Israel and Palestine,
此成功將滴流到  許多其他的外交矛盾
that success will trickle down to a hundred  other diplomatic dilemmas
存在於回教徒  猶太人與基督徒之間…
between Muslims, Jews, Christians...
很高興你提到以色列和巴勒斯坦  因為就在轉播前
I'm glad you brought up Israel and Palestine,  because just before we came on the air,
我收到了一份還未出刊的報導
I received an advance copy of an article  that's going to be
明天《華府先軀報》的頭條
in tomorrow's Washington Herald.  It's front page.
出自喬伊邦斯之筆
And it was written by Zoe Barnes.
她引述《威廉大學學報》  一篇社論
And in it she quotes an editorial that ran  in the Williams College Register
1978年9月  當時你是擔任編輯
when you were editor,  back in September 1978,
聲稱以色列在加薩走廊  和約旦河西岸的市民
which called the Israeli presence  in the Gaza Strip and West Bank, quote,
「是非法侵佔」
"An illegal occupation. "
- 可以讓我看看嗎？  - 當然
-May I see that?  -Sure.
你是否寫下「非法侵佔」？
Did you write those words,  "Illegal occupation"?
不
No.
- 不記得有這事  - 但你當時是此報的編輯
-I have no memory of this.  -But you were the editor of the paper.
是
Yes.
所以這一定得經過你的批准
So it couldn't have gone out  without your approval.
當然不，但我下面的人…
No, of course not. But my staff...
通常都是由別人寫…  然後我們再投票…
Somebody else usually wrote the...  And then we'd vote...
你當時支持這篇社論嗎？
Well, did you vote for it?
說真的，喬治，我不記得了  都35年前的事了…
Honestly, George, I can't remember.  It was 35 years ago...
所以你也不確定  當時有沒有支持這些話
So you're not sure whether or not  you supported these words.
我可以很確定地告訴你  那不是我寫的
I can tell you without a shadow of a doubt,  I did not write these words.
但那是否符合你當時的想法？
But were they in line  with your thinking at the time?
荒謬，太荒謬了
This is ludicrous. It's ludicrous.
太好了，他竟然還笑
That's all we need, him laughing.
南茜，幫我打給  反誹謗聯盟的丹尼斯曼德
Nancy, get me Dennis Mendel at the ADL.
- 中東是美國重要的利益  - 是
-The Middle East is a vital American interest.  -Yes.
你對中東的看法至關緊要
What you think about the Middle East  is relevant.
你可以去查我的投票紀錄
You can look at my voting record.
每一票都是捍衛以色列
Every single vote has  been in defense of Israel.
你的看法何時改變的？
So when did your views change?
我要說的是…  現在重要的是，喬治
What I'm saying to you is...  What's important now, George,
我在代表科羅拉多州時  如何投票
is how I have voted while I have  represented the great state of Colorado.
這是你的立場
I understand that's your position.
但許多人看了或許會覺得
But a lot of other people  are going to look at it and think
你當時的想法也很重要
what you thought then is relevant as well.
那我問你，你的觀點  自大學後是否有改變？
Let me ask you this, have you  ever changed your views since college?
當然，但我不是國務卿候選人
Certainly. But I'm not  the nominee for Secretary of State.
- 就算我真有這種觀點…  - 太棒了
-Even if I did have this viewpoint...  -It's golden.
正中要害
It's a bull's-eye.
你剛才說什麼來著？
What were you saying when you came in?
所以…
So...
我找到凱恩  在大學當編輯時的同事
I found a guy who was on the  college editorial staff when Kern was there.
這傢伙還在活動房屋裏
This burn-out still pumping  mimeograph manifestos
油印一大堆宣言
out of a trailer park in the Berkshires.
但你不打算找他談話
But you're not planning on talking to him.
彼得魯索
Peter Russo.
很好
Good.
聽起來再適合不過了
Sounds like a perfect match.
丹尼斯
Dennis.
你在看斯特凡諾普洛斯嗎？
Any chance  you're watching Stephanopoulos?
你在改善勤勞賓州人的生活時  看起來真性感
You look sexy when you're improving the  lives of hardworking Pennsylvanians.
是改善生活這件事  還是因為這條運動褲？
Is it the improving lives,  or is it these fetching sweat pants?
不如你把電腦拿開  讓我好好看看？
Why don't you move that computer out  of the way, let me see what that looks like?
- 用電腦遮住比較好看  - 去死啦
-Yeah, it's better with the laptop.  -Fuck off.
你都不理我
You're not paying enough attention to me.
我每天在公司看你還不夠嗎？
I pay attention to you all day at the office.
但我好像從未看過你刷牙
Hey, you know, I don't think  I've ever seen you brush your teeth before.
- 一定有吧  - 沒有印象
-Sure you have.  -No, I don't think so.
我知道你會刷牙  只是從來沒看過
I mean, I know that you do brush. But I don't  think I've ever actually witnessed it before.
就是這個樣子
Well, here it is in all its glory.
那是我的牙刷嗎？
Is that my toothbrush?
- 不知道，是嗎？  - 是
-I don't know, is it?  -Yes, it is.
- 你留在這的？  - 彼得，好噁心
-You left it here.  -Peter, gross.
拜託，我們吃了對方不少口水吧
Come on.  We've exchanged plenty of fluids by now.
不要
No, no, no, no.
- 不，牙膏啊！  - 那不是牙膏
-No. Toothpaste!  -It's not toothpaste.
- 我有狂犬病！  - 不要啊！
-I'm rabid!  -No!
去接吧
Go get it.
我必須要接
I have to take this.
我是魯索
This is Russo.
現在12點53分
Yeah. Right now, it's 1 2:53.
好的
Okay, okay, okay.
我得走了
I have to go.
怎麼了？
Is everything okay?
- 公事  - 什麼公事？
-It's work stuff.  -What kind of work stuff?
是威倫斯基議員  他要跟我討論稅收優惠的事
Congressman Wilensky. He wants to  go over the tax incentive stuff we sent him.
彼得，現在是凌晨1點
Peter, it's 1:00 in the morning.
彼得！
Hey, Peter!
我明天要開會  還有委員會的聽證會…
I have meetings tomorrow.  I have a committee hearing...
國會少你一天不會垮的
Congress will survive without you.
地址和路線，幫你買的機票
Address. Directions.  There's an e-ticket in your name.
6點半的飛機  你該出發去機場了
Your flight leaves at 6:30.  You should head to the airport.
法蘭的意思？
This is coming from Frank?
不，不是任何人的意思
No. This is coming from no one.
你今天感冒要請病假
You have the flu and you're calling in sick.
- 那是什麼？  - 什麼是什麼？
-What's that?  -What's what?
那是吻痕嗎？
Is that a hickey?
你又開始嫖妓了？
Are you whoring around again?
不，我有女朋友
No. I have a girlfriend.
你是指你的辦公室戀情
You mean your little office romance.
你知道些什麼？
What do you know about that?
彼得，就我對你人生的瞭解程度
When it comes to your life, Peter,  and what I know about it,
你應該是沒什麼秘密
you should assume that  there's no such thing as a secret.
保持連絡
Stay in touch.
有事打我手機  千萬別打到公司
You call me on my cell, never at the office.
祝你好運
Good luck.
加油
Knock 'em dead, tiger.
怎麼樣？
How are we?
很累、喝很多咖啡  但有進展
Over-tired, under-caffeinated,  but we're making progress.
剩不到一周了
Less than a week to go.
- 我們會盡力  - 你們會怎樣？
-Yeah, we'll do our best.  -You what?
我們會完成
We'll get it done.
誰把窗戶打開吧  裏面臭氣薰天
And somebody open a window.  It's rancid in here.
六個人三、四天不洗澡  就是這個樣子
That is what happens when six people  don't shower for half a week.
除了除臭劑還需要什麼？
Anything you need, other than deodorant?
成績標準這塊
Yeah, this performance standards thing.
- 教師工會恐怕會…  - 留著
-The teachers unions are gonna...  -Leave it in.
- 或許措辭…  - 工會我來搞定
-But we could dilute it a bit...  -I'll handle the unions.
- 還有什麼嗎？  - 開放配偶探視？
-What else, anything?  -Conjugal visits?
我繼續工作
I'll get back to work.
南茜，下面行程是什麼？
Nancy, what do I have next?
2點10分到35分接聽選民電話  募款活動到3點50分
Constituent calls from 2:10 to 2:35,  fundraising until 3:50,
- 4點副黨鞭會議  - 電話名冊？
-deputy caucus at 4:00.  -The call list?
- 在你桌上  - 會議的簡報呢？
-It's on your desk.  -My briefing for the caucus?
- 在名冊旁邊  - 你去過會議室了嗎？
-Next to the call list.  -Have you been in the conference room?
週末找人來蒸汽清潔
Have it steam-cleaned over the weekend.
給這些可憐的小鬼們  幾罐芳香劑
In the meantime, get those poor kids  some Febreze or something.
味道像動物園一樣
It's like a petting zoo.
你快來看
You gotta see this.
但那是否符合你當時的立場？
But were they in line with  your thinking at the time?
我們不認為  以色列和巴勒斯坦關係是兒戲
We do not consider the issue of  Israel and Palestine a laughing matter.
他說以色列「非法」？  他是反猶分子，也有失道德
And he calls Israel "illegal"?  Well, he's an anti-Semite and he is wrong.
要指派這人出任下屆國務卿
We would have grave, grave concerns  about appointing such a man
非常令人擔憂
our next Secretary of State.
輕而易舉
It's too easy.
真正的事實  羅伊卡普奈的部落格
羅伊，你好  我是彼得魯索議員
Roy. Hi, my name is Peter Russo.  Congressman Russo.
我想跟你聊一下…
I'd like to just speak to you for just...
- 先生？  - 你要不就在撒謊，快給我滾
-Sir?  -Either you're lying, and you can fuck off,
不然就在說實話  這樣你就更該給我滾
or you're telling the truth,  and you can absolutely fuck off.
我拜讀了你的網站  我是你的粉絲
I saw your web site. I'm a fan.
我有東西要給你
And I brought you something.
寶貝，把衣服穿上
Babe, put some clothes on.
什麼？
What?
- 我們有客人  - 那又怎樣？
-We got a guest.  -So?
- 你好  - 把衣服穿上
-Hey.  -Put some clothes on.
要不要冰塊？
Ice or no ice?
不要
No ice.
很好，要也沒有
Good, 'cause we don't have any.
- 該死，艾可！我叫你把…  - 不要緊
-Fuck. Echo! I told you to put the...  -It's okay.
若你幫我保密  我就幫你保密
I'll keep your secret if you keep mine.
你說你是議員？
A congressman, you say?
現在我只是個酒伴
Right now, I'm just a drinking companion.
好吧，酒伴，喝一杯吧
Well all right, companion,  have yourself a drink.
進來
Come on in.
一萬元
$10,000.
有什麼服務？
What will that get me?
我有特殊怪僻，但不知道  你是不是要找這種女人
I mean, I'm kinky, but I don't know  if I'm the girl you're looking for.
你果然是我要找的女人
You're definitely the girl that I'm looking for.
抱歉
Excuse me.
這錢是遮口費
All I want for that money is your silence.
- 什麼？  - 那天跟你一起的那個男的
-My what?  -The guy you were with the other night,
被警察逮捕的那個  你知道他是誰嗎？
the one who was arrested.  Do you know who he was?
你是指那個議員？
You mean the congressman?
從來就沒什麼議員
There was no congressman.
也沒人被逮捕  這些全都沒發生過
There was no arrest. None of that exists.
唯一真實的只有你眼前的錢
All that exists is the money  sitting right there in front of you.
明白嗎？
Do you understand?
明白
Yeah.
很好
Good.
張開嘴
Open your mouth.
這是為我做的
Last little bit's for me.
你在罵我
You're scolding me.
有嗎？
Am l?
在你心裏
You are. Silently.
因為健身器材的事？
Is it the rowing machine?
- 你說呢？  - 果然是為了健身器材
-You tell me.  -It's the rowing machine.
你都沒用
You haven't used it.
你怎麼知道？
How do you know I haven't?
法蘭斯
Francis.
你知道我不喜歡被操控
You know I don't like to be managed.
我沒有操控你
I'm not trying to manage you.
我只是不想比你多活25年
I just don't want to outlive you by 25 years.
我每天在國會大樓走五公里  成天在走動
I must walk three miles a day around  that Capitol. I'm constantly on my feet.
你知道用腦要消耗多少大卡嗎？
And do you know how many calories  the brain burns?
我不擔心你的腦
I'm not worried about your brain.
是你的心臟
It's your heart we're talking about.
用健身器材
Use the machine.
她說得對  我是該好好照顧身體
She's right.  I should take better care of myself.
但這是原則問題
But it's the principle.
我絕不成為任何人  或是郵購東西的奴隸
I won't be a slave to anybody or anything  you can order with a toll-free number.
共享這個共和國的財富
We share the wealth in this republic.
我以為整個編輯部都有貢獻
I thought the whole editorial team pitched in.
有時是這樣，但那次沒有
Sometimes. Not that time, though.
但一定有部分是他寫的
But he must've written some of it.
不，整篇都是我寫的
No, that was all me.
若大家認為是他寫的呢？
What if people thought he wrote it.
去他的，他是個虛偽的人
Fuck that, he's a fraud.
不，比虛偽還要糟  他是場該死的鬧劇
No, he's worse than a fraud,  he's a fucking farce.
我告訴你
And I'll tell you something.
他以前比我還要瘋狂
He used to be even more  of a maniac than I am.
- 吸毒？  - 不，政治
-Chemicals?  -No, politics.
有些晚上真的很誇張
We had some nights, man.
徹夜長談  一些很聳動的念頭
Long conversations.  Dangerous fucking notions.
- 例如？  - 隨便你說
-Like what?  -You name it.
油盟、皮諾契、糧食券法案
OPEC, Pinochet,  the fucking Food Stamp Act,
然後祖國開始勾引他
then the motherland sang her mating call.
你看見了嗎…
Oh, say can you...
接著他惡補考上  布林茅爾學院法學院，開始從政
Next thing, he's cramming for the bar  at Bryn Mawr and snapping on a flag pin.
布林茅爾有法學院嗎？
Does Bryn Mawr have a law school?
我的重點是他開始像個牆頭草
My point is, he started goose-stepping  in the marionette parade.
左派、右派、紅、藍  民主黨、共和黨
Left, right, red, blue, Democrat, Republican.
追根究底還不是都一個樣
They're all dangling from the same strings.
還不如把一切都毀滅
Take a sledge hammer to the whole fucking  Punch and Judy show,
這才是必須的
that's what's required.
我還以為你很愛國
Thought you were a patriot.
- 當然，當今沒剩幾個了  - 那當公僕有何不妥？
-Fuck yeah, one of the few.  -So what's wrong with public service?
公僕？拜託
Public service? Come on, man.
你得搞清楚老大是誰
You gotta get a grip  on who your masters are.
國際貨幣基金組織、世界銀行  洛克斐勒三邊委員會
The lMF, the World Bank,  the Rockefeller Trilateral Commission.
他們的行刑隊都是你在養
You bank roll their fucking death squads.
名叫聯邦緊急事務管理署  煙酒槍炮及爆裂物管理局
It's called FEMA, it's called  Alcohol, Tobacco and Firearms.
北約、邊境管理
NATO, border control.
卡崔娜颶風應變是無能嗎？  那是刻意串通好的疏忽
You think Katrina was incompetence?  That was highly orchestrated negligence.
你看圍城事件、國際特赦組織  美國公民自由聯盟
Look at Waco, Amnesty lnternational,  the ACLU.
都是煙霧彈，手上都染血
Smoke screens, all of them.  Blood on their hands.
正是啊
Well, exactly.
你要我欺騙人民
You want me to lie to the people.
我要你除去另一個偽君子  拯救人民
I want you to spare the people  another hypocrite.
你有什麼好處？
What's in it for you?
算是討回公道
Poetic justice.
你也是他們的一分子
Come on, you're one of them.
大集團的走狗  卷大麻的技巧有這麼熟練嗎？
Can a corporate sell-out roll a joint like this?
若真要這麼做
If I wanted to do this thing,
應該要做些什麼呢？
how might I go about that, precisely?
怎麼樣？
How did it go?
有些人哭了，有些人很憤怒
There were a few tears here and there  and some anger,
但都在預料之內
but nothing unexpected.
我今天也要開除你，艾薇琳
I'm going to need you to leave us  today too, Evelyn.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我不能留下質疑我決策的人
I just can't have any doubt  about the direction I'm taking.
- 你才剛逼我炒了18個人  - 我知道
-You just had me fire 18 people.  -I know.
我坐在他們對面
I sat across from them in this room,
- 必須跟每一個人說…  - 我知道
-and I had to tell each and every one...  -I know.
我已經59歲了  沒有人會僱用我
I am 59 years old.  Nobody hires anybody my age.
我願意幫你寫任何推薦信…
I will write you  any kind of recommendation...
幹嘛？幫人裝菜嗎？
To do what? Bag groceries?
拜託，我要怎麼跟女兒說？
Come on, what am l  supposed to tell my daughter?
我真的很抱歉，艾薇琳…
I'm sorry, Evelyn, I truly...
你根本不在乎
No, you're not. You don't give a fuck.
18個人，克萊兒
Eighteen people, Claire.
加上我就19個
Nineteen if you count me.
我必須…
I have to...
我必須打電話給我女兒
I have to call my daughter.
我知道今天很難熬
I know today has been tough.
你們很多同事都離開了
A lot of your colleagues have left,
我必須要向你們解釋
and I owe you an explanation.
今天離開的人  許多都是淨水創權的元老
Many of those who left us today helped  build the CWl from the ground up,
我很感謝他們
and I'm grateful to them.
但我們現在必須要進化
But it is time for us to evolve,
為了這個目標  我們必須做出困難的選擇
and to accomplish this,  we had to make hard choices
招攬新人
and bring in new people.
這就是今天的意義
That's what today was about.
任何人若有疑問  可以隨時來找我
You have any questions,  my door is always open.
全國和地方新聞都搞定了  若有需要，政治版有留版面
I'm all good for National and Metro.  We've got space for Political if we need it.
珍妮？麥克凱恩那有新消息嗎？
Janine? Anything new on Michael Kern?
白宮在打太極
The White House is dodging.
沒有人願意正式發言？
You can't get anyone on record?
不只是我  他們禁止所有問題
Not just me. They're shutting  all of us down in the briefings.
連幕後都沒人肯吭一聲
No one is giving an inch,  even on background.
在這期間，我在寫
In the meantime,  I'm working on a feature about
總統府外交政策的特別報導
the administration's foreign policy agenda,
從競選時承諾  要增加國防部預算轉變為…
how it shifted from the start of the campaign,  increased DOD spending...
看到你了，喬伊
We see you, Zoe.
我找到凱恩  和那篇社論的直接關係
I can link Kern  directly to the Williams editorial.
- 什麼？  - 我找到一個叫羅伊卡普奈的人
-What?  -I've got a guy named Roy Kapeniak,
凱恩當編輯時他也在編輯部
who was on the editorial staff  when Kern was there.
推特小賤人，搞什麼鬼啊？
Hey, Twitter-twat. WTF?
等等，羅伊什麼？
Wait, wait, wait. Roy what?
卡普奈，他是凱恩的同學
Kapeniak. A classmate of Kern's.
他說那篇社論  每個字都是凱恩寫的
I have him on record saying  Kern wrote every word of the editorial.
喬伊、盧卡斯，到我辦公室
Let's move this into my office. Zoe, Lucas.
珍妮！
Janine!
容我一次把話講清楚
Let me once and for all say this definitively.
那篇社論不是我寫的
I didn't author that editorial.
一字一句或標點符號都不是
Not a single sentence,  word, comma or period.
我若沒記錯的話  應該是位卡普奈先生寫的
If memory serves me,  it was Mr. Kapeniak who wrote it.
他為何一口咬定說是我寫的  我無從得知
Why on earth he's trying to claim that I did  is beyond me.
但我必須進一步聲明  我非常支持以色列
Let me further say that I am  a strong supporter of the state of Israel.
它是中東地區最穩定的國家  也是我們最有力的盟友…
As the most stable country in the region  and our strongest ally...
法蘭安德沃找凱西
It's Frank Underwood for Cathy.
…推動任何和平政策
...in any peace process.
因為少了以色列的穩定性  就不可能有巴勒斯坦
Because without the stability of Israel,  there can be no Palestine.
馬上看CNN
CNN, right now.
- 「少了以色列就不可能有巴勒斯坦」？  - 我在看
-"Without Israel there can be no Palestine"?  -I've got it on.
我想要提醒凱恩參議員  巴勒斯坦早就存在
I would remind Senator Kern  that there was a Palestine
早在以色列成立前就存在了
Iong before there was an Israel.
他的發言不但無知  還含有種族歧視
His comments are not only ignorant,  they are racist.
做好準備，凱西  後面發展將非常快
Get ready, Cathy.  Things are about to move very quickly.
好的，我準備好了
Okay, I'm ready.
- 你好，我…  - 彼得
-Hey. I...  -Peter.
- 現在沒時間  - 等等！你去哪裏了？
-Not now.  -Stop! Hey, hey, where have you been?
- 天啊，你在嗑藥  - 不，我…
-God, you're fucking high.  -No, l...
你是，你看你的眼睛
Yes, you are, look at your eyes.
別管了
Please, just lay off.
你答應我你不會再這樣的
You promised me it wouldn't be like this.
把我今天的行程都取消
Cancel whatever I have  for the rest of the day.
凱恩沒戲唱了
Kern is out.
- 他們甩掉他了？  - 嚴格來說，是他自己退出
-They're tossing him?  -Technically, he'll withdraw himself, but yes.
能說「白宮的可靠消息」嗎？
Can I say,  "A source close to the White House"?
不，讓消息自己散出去
No. You let this story  play out on its own time.
他們明早就會宣佈了
They'll announce in the morning.
抱歉，如果不是那件事  那是什麼新聞？
I'm sorry, if not that,  what story are we talking about?
凱薩琳杜倫  凱恩一退出，你就報由她接手
Catherine Durant. As soon as Kern  withdraws, you say she'll be the replacement.
- 是真的嗎？  - 你登了就是
-ls that true?  -lt will be after you write it.
羅伊卡普奈是你的棋子
Roy Kapeniak was you.
你是可以這麼想  我不予置評
You might very well think that.  I couldn't possibly comment.
你找到他，要他跟我連絡…
You found him. You had him call me...
卡普奈與凱恩只是前菜  邦斯小姐
Kapeniak and Kern were appetizers,  Ms. Barnes.
凱薩琳杜倫才是主菜
Catherine Durant is the meal.
說那個名字「凱薩琳杜倫」  重複地念
Say that name. "Catherine Durant."  Say it over and over.
明天下午，將名字寫下來
Tomorrow afternoon, write it down.
然後等著從美國總統的口中  聽到這個名字
Then watch that name come out of the mouth  of the President of the United States.
這就是我們要創造的事
This is where we get to create.
別錯過你的班車，邦斯小姐  這可是末班車
Don't miss your train, Ms. Barnes.  It's the last one tonight.
《華府先軀報》喬伊邦斯報導
Zoe Barnes of the Washington Herald  now reporting,
總統身邊的可靠消息指出  凱薩琳杜倫參議員
quoting a source close to the President,  as saying that Senator Catherine Durant
很可能是下屆國務卿人選
will likely be the new nominee  for Secretary of State
麥克凱恩這周宣佈退出
after Michael Kern's withdrawal  earlier this week.
白宮對於總統是否會提名杜倫
The White House has remained silent  on whether the President
目前並沒有任何表示
will tap Durant for the nomination,
但全國佐格比民調顯示  兩黨對杜倫的支持度都非常高
but a national Zogby poll shows  wide support for Durant across party lines.
…在參議院外交關係委員會  服務長達十年
...has served 10 years on  the Senate Foreign Relations Committee,
曾多次參與外交任務  造訪南美…
made numerous diplomatic missions  to South America...
…信任她，知道我們選了一名  有責任感、經驗豐富
...place our faith in her, knowing that  we have a responsible, experienced,
和聰明的女人  代表我們的國外權益
brilliant woman representing  our interests abroad.
…中堅分子、能與他人合作  在國防上採取強硬態度
...middle of the road, team player,  strong on defense.
她確實可與三軍參謀共事
And if there's a woman that can work  with the Joint Chiefs, she's the one.
杜倫絕對是最佳人選
Durant is the way to go, it's a no-brainer.
總統應該停止做秀  盡快公佈人選
The President should stop this pageant  and simply make the call.
我們為什麼還在猜測  是否會推選杜倫？
Why are we still talking about  if they're going to nominate Durant?
為什麼不快點宣佈  我們就能結束這種推測
Why don't they just do it already  so we can all stop talking about ifs
改討論時間與細節
and start talking about when and what
還有杜倫會如何影響  美國外交政策
and how Durant's going  to shape our foreign policy.
歷史呢？
So, history?
歷史
History.
我很滿意，法蘭
I'm very impressed, Frank.
很好，你批了  我就可以開始編輯
Good. With your go-ahead,  I'll start the mark-up.
柏許跟拉斯穆森看過了嗎？
Have Birch and Rasmussen seen this?
還沒，我想先讓你過目
Not yet, I wanted you to be  the first to have a look.
我會幫你跟總統約時間  向他匯報
I'll schedule a time for you  to fill in the President.
不，那是你的地盤，琳達  應該由你去
Oh, no, no, no. That is your turf, Linda.  You should do that.
- 謝謝你，法蘭  - 我的榮幸，謝謝
-Thank you, Frank.  -My pleasure. Thank you.
我為之前的事道歉…
I so apologize for everything...
不，真的不需要
No, no, no. That's not necessary.
現在才是真正的會議
Now for the real meeting.
麥克凱恩到底怎麼回事？
So, what is happening with Michael Kern?
- 簡直是場噩夢  - 你們知道要找誰代替嗎？
-It's a total nightmare.  -Do you know who you're going to tap next?
法蘭，我們需要你在眾議院…
Frank, we still need you in the House...
不，我壓根沒這麼想  我們有教育提案的事要忙
No, no, no. I wouldn't dream of it.  We've got our education bill.
我只是好奇
I was just curious.
有傳言說  我們要提名凱薩琳杜倫
Somehow, the rumor is flying around that  we're going to nominate Catherine Durant.
我相信你也有耳聞
I'm sure you've noticed.
是真的嗎？
Is the rumor true?
本來是沒有考慮她
Well, we weren't considering her at first,
但總統已經吩咐我調查她  若最後決定提名她
but the President asked me to have  her vetted, in case we want to go that route.
真有趣
Interesting.
你認為呢？
What do you think?
她不會是我的首選…
Well, she wouldn't be my first choice...
你的首選是誰呢？
Who would be your first choice?
她在初選時跟我們是對立的
She campaigned hard against us  in the primaries.
這也是我的顧慮
That's my reservation.
但這樣反而顯得你們肚量大
But you'd show yourself  above party politics,
我相信她會更努力爭取
and I know she'd work all the harder for it.
經驗也足夠  兩黨對她都有一定的尊敬…
Decent experience.  Respect across the aisle...
你認為真的可以考慮她？
So you think we can seriously consider her?
不是個壞點子
It's not the worst idea in the world.
你哪來的消息？
Where are you getting this shit?
- 什麼？  - 你的新聞
-What?  -Your stories.
- 我只是…  - 你在陪誰睡？
-I was just...  -Who are you fucking?
- 沒有人  - 拜託
-Nobody.  -Oh, come on.
你本來是地方新聞的小咖  現在看看你
You're a Metro scrub, and now look at you.
你一定是跟哪個大人物上床
You'd have to be fucking  somebody important.
我只是在做我的工作，珍妮  失陪了
I'm just doing my job, Janine. Excuse me.
好吧，等一下，好
All right. One sec. Okay.
- 這是你第一次連線？  - 對，第一次
-ls this your first remote?  -Yeah, it's my first time.
看鏡頭
Right into the camera.
彆扭來扭去
Don't shift in your seat,  and there's no reason
講話不需要太大聲  麥克風收音很好
to speak above a conversational volume,  the mic will pick you up.
- 好了嗎？  - 好了
-You all ready?  -Yeah.
別忘了要呼吸
All right, don't forget to breathe.
5、4、3…  Five, four, three...
我們歡迎  《華府先軀報》的喬伊邦斯
We'd like to welcome Zoe Barnes  from the Washington Herald.
喬伊，謝謝你的加入
Zoe, thank you forjoining us.
我很榮幸，謝謝你們的邀情
I am very glad to be here.  Thank you for having me.
你獨家報導教育提案  凱恩的社論，現在又加上杜倫
You broke the education bill,  the Kern editorial and now Durant.
我很興奮  能報導重要的新聞
I'm just thrilled to be reporting  news that matters.
這是《先軀報》  整個團隊的努力
And it's truly been a team effort.  Everyone at the Herald pitched in.
但確實有許多第一次
But yes, a lot of firsts.
第一個全國性新聞，第一個…
First national story, first...
謝謝
Thank you.
- 我先走了  - 明天見，先生
-Calling it a night.  -See you tomorrow, sir.
確實有許多第一次
But yes, a lot of firsts.
第一個全國性新聞  第一個頭條新聞
First national story, first front page by-line,
第一個電視採訪…
first TV interview...
我很想跟我媽揮手  但攝影師叫我別亂動
I would wave to my mom, but the camera man  said not to shift in my seat.
真像是雲霄飛車
What a roller coaster.
太可惜了，凱恩是個好人
It really is too bad. Kern is a good man.
現在輪到凱薩琳杜倫
And now Catherine Durant.
我想這就是所謂的  天時地利人和吧
Yes. Right place, right time, I suppose.
- 我們喜歡她，不是嗎？  - 非常喜歡
-We like her, don't we?  -Very much.
重點是她是否  也這麼喜歡善可工業？
The question is does she like  SanCorp as much as we like her?
那是很好的賭注
I would say that that is a very good bet.
但話說回來  我不是個愛賭的人
But then again, I'm not a betting man.
你總是喜歡有把握的事
No, you always like a sure thing.
如果能夠的話，晚安，瑞米
When it avails itself. Goodnight, Remy.
晚安，法蘭，後會有期
Goodnight, Frank. See you around.
希望越來越少
Hopefully less and less now.
抱歉，我算錯了  你點的是什麼？
Oh, no, I charged the wrong thing.  What did you have again?
中杯無因拿鐵
Medium decaf latte.
中杯無因拿鐵…
Med, latt, dec...
- 我不知道怎麼退出去  - 按這個然後這個
-I don't know how to get it to go back.  -This one and this one.
- 這個？  - 不是，我來吧
-This one?  -No. Let me do it.
我必須請你退後，議員
I'll have to ask you  to stay back, Congressman.
怎麼了？
What's going on?
有個人想要闖進去
Some guy was trying to get into the building.
我們把他攔下來後  他突然開始脫衣服
When we said no,  he started tearing his clothes off.
沒有人聽得到你  也沒有人在乎你
Nobody can hear you.  Nobody cares about you.
這一點意義都沒有
Nothing will come of this.
不如讓這兩個人送你回家？
Why don't you let these nice gentlemen  take you home?
找東西給他蓋，外面很冷
Cover him up. It's cold out here.
你聽到議員說的了  找東西給他蓋
You heard the congressman. Cover him up.
法蘭斯？
Francis?